Welcome back.
欢迎回来。
In this video, let's look at a variety of puzzles related to the reference variables.
在这个视频中，让我们看看与参考变量有关的各种难题。
We'll try and understand in depth about the reference variables, different concepts like equality of
我们将尝试并深入了解引用变量，不同的概念，如引用变量的相等
reference variables, initialization of reference variables, and assigning reference variables.
参考变量的平等，参考变量的初始化，以及分配参考变量。
Let's look at all of them in this video.
让我们在这个视频中看看所有的内容。
Let's get started.
让我们开始吧。
Let's say I'm just saying Animal nothing and creating this.
比方说，我只是说动物什么都没有，然后创建这个。
What would be the value which is assigned to nothing?
分配给nothing的值是什么？
As you can see, it's null and how is this stored? The way nothing is stored is, because we did not create
正如你所看到的，它是null，这是如何存储的呢？Nothing的存储方式是，因为我们没有创建
anything,
任何东西。
nothing is created
什么都没有被创建
and in here the value which is stored is null.
在这里，被存储的值是空的。
That's basically means it does not have a memory location present. So, it's empty.
这基本上意味着它没有一个内存位置存在。所以，它是空的。
It's kind of empty. Null refers to empty.
它是一种空的。Null指的是空。
So, null here means, it's not referring to anything. It's a reference variable but as of now nothing is
所以，null在这里意味着，它没有提到任何东西。它是一个引用变量，但从目前来看，什么都不是
referring to nothing.
指向任何东西。
I would want to store the reference to cat in nothing.
我想在nothing中存储对猫的引用。
What would happen?
会发生什么呢？
I'll say nothing = cat.
我就说nothing = cat。
Now, you can see that, you can see the memory location here is same as this,
现在，你可以看到，你可以看到这里的内存位置与此相同。
right.
对。
When I do nothing = cat,
当我做nothing = cat时。
what happens is, where is cat stored?
会发生什么，cat被储存在哪里？
1C, that gets copied into, into the memory location of nothing.
1C，它被复制到了nothing的内存位置。
So, basically we are not doing anything with the objects. So, when we are saying nothing = cat,
所以，基本上我们没有对这些对象做任何事情。所以，当我们说无=猫的时候。
what is happening is the, from the cat reference variable, the location of where the cat object is stored
所发生的是，从cat引用变量中，cat对象的存储位置
that is getting copied into nothing.
被复制到nothing中。
That's basically what is happening in here.
这基本上就是这里发生的事情。
So, if I say nothing.id = 10, what would be the value of cat.id?
所以，如果我说nothing.id=10，cat.id的值会是什么？
What do you think would be the value of cat.id?
你认为cat.id的值会是多少呢？
It's also 10, because the way it would work is nothing.id,
它也是10，因为它的工作方式是nothing.id。
nothing is referring to which object? nothing
nothing指的是哪个对象？
is referring to 1C.
指的是1C。
So, what would happen? Here,
那么，会发生什么呢？这里。
the object at 1C would be changed.
1C的对象将被改变。
So, I am changing the value of it to 10.
所以，我把它的值改为10。
So, what would happen? This value becomes 10. The value inside the object becomes 10.
那么，会发生什么？这个值变成了10。对象里面的值变成了10。
So, now the value which is pointed to by cat is also referring to the same thing.
所以，现在cat所指向的值也指的是同一个东西。
So, it has a value of 10.
所以，它的值是10。
This is very important concept to understand, right.
这是非常重要的概念，要理解，对吧。
When we copy reference variables, when I say nothing = cat, what gets copied is the memory location
当我们复制引用变量时，当我说nothing = cat时，被复制的是内存位置
where the cat is stored. That gets copied into nothing.
储存猫的地方。这将被复制到nothing中。
Let's say, now I would say dog = nothing. What would happen? If I say dog = nothing,
比方说，现在我说dog = nothing。会发生什么？如果我说狗=无。
1C gets copied into 1A. I'll not do that.
1C就会被复制到1A。我不会那样做。
What I'll do is I'll say nothing = dog.
我将做的是我将说无=狗。
What will happen now?
现在会发生什么？
Nothing = dog, right.
无=狗，对。
So, what would happen?
那么，会发生什么呢？
The memory location of dog gets stored into nothing.
狗的内存位置被存储到nothing中。
Now, if I say nothing.id, whose id is printed? nothing.id would print the id of the dog, 1A 12,
现在，如果我说nothing.id，会打印谁的id？ nothing.id会打印狗的id，1A 12。
right. So let's print. It's
对。所以，让我们打印吧。它是
printing 12. So, it's very important to understand what's happening in the background, so that you'd
打印12。所以，了解后台发生的事情是非常重要的，这样你就可以
be able to exactly know what's happening in here.
这样你就能确切地知道这里正在发生什么。
However, in the case of primitive variables, what would happen? If I say int j = i,
然而，在原始变量的情况下，会发生什么？如果我说int j = i。
what would happen?
会发生什么？
j gets a value of 5, right. So, j is created with a value of 5
j得到一个5的值，对。所以，j被创建时的值是5
and even if I change the value of j,
即使我改变了j的值。
the only thing which gets modified is j.
唯一被修改的就是j。
So, with the case of primitive variables what you are storing here is the value.
所以，在原始变量的情况下，你在这里存储的是值。
So, if I type in i, i would still have a value of 5.
因此，如果我输入i，i的值仍然是5。
However, with the case of reference variables, what we are storing is the memory location. When I copy
然而，在引用变量的情况下，我们所存储的是内存位置。当我复制
a reference variable, what gets copied is the reference to the memory location where the actual object
参考变量时，被复制的是实际对象所在的内存位置的参考
is getting stored.
被存储的内存位置的引用。
Now, let's say i == j, what would happen? i == j
现在，让我们假设i == j，会发生什么？
is a false, because i has a different value as j.
是一个假的，因为i的值和j不同。
Now, let's say I copy the value of j = 5,
现在，让我们说我复制了j=5的值。
right. So, i and j now have same values.
对。所以，i和j现在有相同的值。
So, if I say i == j, what would happen?
那么，如果我说i == j，会发生什么？
It has a value of true, right. Now,
它的值是真，对。现在。
let's take the case of the reference variables. Let's try and recreate the same objects again.
让我们来看看引用变量的情况。让我们再试着重新创建同样的对象。
So, let's say Animal dog = new Animal of, dog is referring to 1A, 12, right? So, let's create
所以，我们说Animal dog = new Animal of，dog是指1A，12，对吗？所以，让我们创建
exactly the same way
完全相同的方式
and cat, earlier was referrring to
而猫，早先指的是
let's say 1C 10,
让我们说1C 10。
right. So, let's say it's 10, cat is referring to here.
对。所以，让我们说是10，猫在这里指的是。
We need to create nothing. Instead of nothing,
我们需要创造无。而不是什么都没有。
I'll call it ref, just a ref.
我就叫它ref，就是一个ref。
So, I'll say Animal ref and what I'll do in here is, I'll assign the reference to cat. What ref stores
所以，我就说Animal ref，我在这里要做的是，我把这个引用分配给cat。ref存储的是
is the reference to the cat. So,
是对猫的引用。所以。
1C.
I'll also create another dog2. Let's say it also has the same value for the id, right.
我还将创建另一个dog2。让我们说，它也有相同的id值，对吧。
So, we are creating another dog2 which will have Animal12.
所以，我们正在创建另一个狗2，它的id是Animal12。
So, let's say, it's stored here, Animal12 and we are calling this dog2
所以，让我们说，它被存储在这里，Animal12，我们正在调用这个dog2
and this is
而这是
at location 1E,
在位置1E。
right. So,
对。所以。
very simple. Now,
非常简单。现在。
over here, let's now try the == operator,
在这里，让我们现在试试==运算符。
right.
对。
So, cat == dog,
所以，猫==狗。
what do you think would be the output? false,
你认为输出结果是什么？ 假的。
because they are not referring to the same object,
因为它们所指的不是同一个对象。
right. That's cool. Now,
对。这很好。现在。
cat == ref,
cat == ref。
Yep.
是的。
They return a true because they're pointing to the exactly the same object, right.
它们返回一个真，因为它们指向的是完全相同的对象，对吗？
So, this is the same object they're referring to.
所以，这就是它们所指的同一个对象。
However, the interesting thing is dog == dog2.
然而，有趣的是dog == dog2。
What do you think will be the output? It says false. Even though they have the same values, that does
你认为输出结果会是什么？它说是假的。尽管它们有相同的值，这并不
not matter.
并不重要。
What is important is the objects they are referring to. The object they're referring to are different.
重要的是它们所引用的对象。它们所引用的对象是不同的。
So, here we are referring to a different object
所以，这里我们指的是一个不同的对象
and here we are referring to a different object. On the heap,
和这里我们指的是一个不同的对象。在堆上。
we are referring to two different objects.
我们指的是两个不同的对象。
So, here 1A and 1E. Even though the values are the same but their locations on the heap are different,
所以，这里是1A和1E。尽管值是一样的，但它们在堆中的位置是不同的。
they are distinct objects on the heap.
它们是堆上不同的对象。
So, the important thing to understand is when we are comparing reference variables using ==,
所以，需要理解的是，当我们使用==来比较引用变量时。
what we are just comparing is, if they're referring to the same object.
我们所要比较的是，如果它们引用的是同一个对象。
If they have references of two different objects, it does not matter even if the values are the same.
如果它们有两个不同对象的引用，即使值是一样的也没有关系。
The answer would be false.
答案将是假的。
The important thing to understand here is the == operator for a primitive variables
这里需要理解的是，原始变量的==操作符
compares the values. But for reference variables, compares if they are referring to the same object.
比较了数值。但是对于引用变量来说，比较的是它们是否引用了同一个对象。
If they are not referring to the same object, it would return false.
如果它们不是指向同一个对象，就会返回错误。
In this video, we discussed how a reference variable is stored in memory,
在这个视频中，我们讨论了引用变量是如何存储在内存中的。
what would happen when I assign a reference variable to another,
当我把一个引用变量分配给另一个引用变量时会发生什么？
and also how do you compare equality of reference variables.
以及如何比较引用变量的平等性。
We learnt that a reference variable, if you do not assign it a value, then it has a value of null
我们了解到，如果你不给引用变量赋值，那么它的值就是null。
and we also learnt that the reference variable points to a location of memory where the actual object
我们还了解到，引用变量指向实际对象所在的内存位置。
is stored and when we compare reference objects what we are comparing is if they are pointing to the
当我们比较引用对象时，我们要比较的是它们是否指向了
same object,
同一个对象。
dog = cat only if they are pointing to the same memory location.
dog = cat，只有当它们指向同一个内存位置时。
cat = ref only if they are pointing to the same memory location and when we are assigning
cat = ref 只有当它们指向相同的内存位置时，当我们将一个引用变量赋值给另一个引用变量时，得到的是什么？
a reference variable to another, what gets copied is the reference of where it is stored in memory.
当我们将一个引用变量赋值给另一个变量时，被复制的是它在内存中存储的引用。
The object does not get copied. All that gets copied is the reference.
对象不会被复制。所有被复制的都是引用。
So, if I say dog = ref, this 1C gets copied into this location.
所以，如果我说dog = ref，这个1C被复制到这个位置。
That's all. The actual object is not really affected.
这就是全部。实际的对象并没有受到真正的影响。
We'll talk about these concepts much more when we talk about garbage collection in a future section.
当我们在以后的章节中讨论垃圾回收时，我们会更多地讨论这些概念。
Until then, bye bye.
在那之前，拜拜了。